

TRUONG THỊ PHƯƠNG SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of Birth10/07/1996GenderFemalePhone number01664653487AddressHoai Tan Ward, Hoai Nhon

Hoai Tan Ward, Hoai Nhon District, Binh Dinh Province

Email truongthiphuong782@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

Take advantages of creative thinking skills and English to become a professional software engineer and bring a lot benefit for company. I want to learn more things when working in environment of company to accumulate much experience for future promotion. I will contribute to development of TMA Solutions.

HOBBY

Reading books
Travelling around anywhere

EDUCATION

8/2014 - Current

University of Science

Major: Faculty of Electronics and

Telecommunications

GPA 7.19

EXPERIENCE

07/2017 - 09/2017

S-Plus Software

Internship

Main responsibilities:

- Write testcase of software
- Test software

03/2018 - 06/2018

TMA Solutions

Internship

Main responsibilities:

- Develop topic "Úng dụng module 2G/3G/4G/GPS trong hệ thống giám sát và chăm sóc sức khỏe từ xa"

SKILLS

English	
Japanese	
Java	
C/C++	
· · ·	
Communicative	
Creative thinking	